{
    "subject": "resource/Taruni_Sachdev",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Taruni Sachdev",
    "human_readable": "The name of Taruni Sachdev is Taruni Sachdev.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9640600085258484,
            "question": "What is Taruni Sachdev's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547944068908691,
            "question": "Is there anyone named Taruni Sachdev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9443804025650024,
            "question": "Does the name 'Taruni Sachdev' refer to someone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9349706172943115,
            "question": "Who is Taruni Sachdev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9297138452529907,
            "question": "Is Taruni Sachdev a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9291154742240906,
            "question": "Is 'Taruni Sachdev' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8524537086486816,
            "question": "How unique is the name 'Taruni Sachdev'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159061431884766,
            "question": "What information do we have about Taruni Sachdev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309291124343872,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Taruni Sachdev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5870442986488342,
            "question": "What else could 'Taruni Sachdev' refer to besides a person?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Taruni Sachdev is Taruni Sachdev.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8697_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Taruni Sachdev?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8697_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information do we have about Taruni Sachdev?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8697_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How unique is the name 'Taruni Sachdev'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8697_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8697_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple \"The name of Taruni Sachdev is Taruni Sachdev\" in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all instances of the document mention \"Taruni Sachdev\" as her full name, without any variation or alternative names being mentioned. Therefore, the triple is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The name of Taruni Sachdev is Taruni Sachdev\" is correct according to the provided documents, as all information about her biography and profession starts with \"Taruni Sachdev Bio\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}